<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Structure on Digital Concert Hall Design System</title>
    <link>/design/structure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Structure on Digital Concert Hall Design System</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/design/structure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakpoints</title>
      <link>/design/structure/breakpoints/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/design/structure/breakpoints/</guid>
      <description>How It Works When designing Digital Concert Hall, it&amp;rsquo;s important that any decision takes into consideration that we support many platforms, and for each, an exponential number of devices, with screens of many sizes.
Each platform has its own way to define how to deal with different device sizes:
 Web uses media queries, with a wide choice of units (px/em/%/&amp;hellip;) iOS &amp;amp; tvOS uses size classes, and point Android uses screen density and density-independent pixels &amp;hellip;  As disparate as all these methods and measurements may be, most responsive sizing issues are global.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grid</title>
      <link>/design/structure/grid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/design/structure/grid/</guid>
      <description>How It Works A flexible grid is crucial when designing a consistent evolving experience across multiple platforms and screen sizes.
Gutters Columns create gutters (gaps between column content) through padding. For devices with a screen width greater than 768px, the column padding is 24px. For devices with a screen width less than 768px, the column padding is 16px.
Columns The Column width is variable, filling up the space left when gutter width and margin has been taken into account.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>